dealgenius.com 2012-11-11

# Privacy Policy for DealGenius.com

**Privacy Policy**

Our success has come from taking care of our customers not selling them! Your privacy is very important to us. 

We collect your information so we can process your orders, provide you with customer support, and keep you posted with what is going on with our website. We also use basic web statistics to track web traffic to our site. 

We may on occassion share your information with a third party to assist with processing your order, but not for their independent use or benefit. 

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you. 

We may use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, google). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

All payments are processed using Paypal even if you supply us with a credit card. No other 3rd party merchant or payment processing companies will have access to your payment information. 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

Future changes may be made to this policy at any time. We will notify you of any changes by sending you an email, or simply updating our website. Any changes take affect after 15 days from such notice.
